At OCP, our mission is to re-imagine
data center, telco, and edge infrastructures
to achieve greater choice,
customization and cost savings,
and OCP solution providers play a vital
role in making that mission a reality
by delivering and supporting
integrated solutions, providing
local engineering architecture resources
for customers, establishing
and maintaining relationships
with manufacturers of OCP products,
taking part in business planning sessions
with the Foundation to better align
with your company's goals,
and of course, actively participating
in the OCP Community.
Interested in becoming a solution provider?
The first thing you'll need to do
is become an OCP Corporate Member
by signing the appropriate provider
agreement and paying the appropriate fee.
The next step is to build
your product based on an approved OCP
specification or design package
if you're a colo solution provider,
to complete the OCP Ready
colo site assessment.
Once you do, you can enroll your product in the OCP
product recognition program for
OCP Accepted approval,
or submit your colo facility
site assessment to our incubation
committee for OCP Ready recognition.
When your product, solution or facility
has been approved, you can get started
marketing your OCP Accepted products, integrated solutions,
or OCP Ready facility on our marketplace
and throughout the world.
By participating in the OCP Community
as a solution provider,
you have the chance to bring greater
efficiencies to your customers’
infrastructure, reach potential adopters,
and most importantly,
contribute to reimagining our world's
IT infrastructure.
Get started at opencompute.org.